tmotor.com 2018-12-28

# T-motor-The Safest Propulsion System

Your privacy is important to T-MOTOR so we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your personal information. In addition to this Privacy Policy, we provide data and privacy information imbedded in our products for certain features that ask to use your personal information. You can review this information before enabling these features, in Settings related to those features.  

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and contact us if you have any questions.

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with T-MOTOR. T-MOTOR may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information T-MOTOR may collect and how we may use it:

 **What personal information we collect**

    When you create an T-MOTOR ID, apply for commercial credit, purchase a product, download a software update, register for a class at an T-MOTOR Retail Store, connect to our services, contact us or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, device identifiers, IP address, location information and credit card information.

    When you share your content with family and friends using T-MOTOR products, send gift certificates and products, or invite others to participate in T-MOTOR services or forums, T-MOTOR may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number. T-MOTOR will use such information to fulfill your requests, provide the relevant product or service, or for anti-fraud purposes.

 **How we use your personal information**

We may process your personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy with your consent, for compliance with a legal obligation to which T-MOTOR is subject or when we have assessed it is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by T-MOTOR or a third party to whom it may be necessary to disclose information.

    The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on T-MOTOR’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.

    We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of T-MOTOR ID account holders.

    From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with T-MOTOR, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

    We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve T-MOTOR’s products, services, and customer communications.

    If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

 **Source of your personal information where they are not collected from you**

We may have received your personal information from other persons if that person has shared their content with you using T-MOTOR products, sent gift certificates and products, or invited you to participate in T-MOTOR services or forums. We may also validate the information provided by you when creating an T-MOTOR ID with a third party for security and fraud prevention purposes.

For research and development purposes, we may use datasets such as those that contain images, voices or other data that could be associated with an identifiable person. When acquiring such datasets, we do so in accordance with applicable law in the jurisdiction in which the dataset is hosted. When using such datasets for research and development, we do not attempt to re-identify individuals who may appear therein.

 **Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

    We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where an T-MOTOR product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.

    We may collect and store details of how you use our services, including search queries. This information may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services. Except in limited instances to ensure quality of our services over the Internet, such information will not be associated with your IP address.

    With your explicit consent, we may collect data about how you use your device and applications in order to help app developers improve their apps.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

 **Disclosure to Third Parties**

At times T-MOTOR may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with T-MOTOR to provide products and services, or that help T-MOTOR market to customers. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by T-MOTOR and respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by T-MOTOR to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

 **Service Providers**

T-MOTOR shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever T-MOTOR operates.

 **Others**

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for T-MOTOR to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

 **Protection of Personal Information**

T-MOTOR takes the security of your personal information very seriously. T-MOTOR online services such as the T-MOTOR Online Store protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). When your personal data is stored by T-MOTOR, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures. With the exception of iCloud Mail, iCloud data is stored in encrypted form including when we utilize third-party storage.

When you use some T-MOTOR products, services, or applications or post on an T-MOTOR forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information and content you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

If you or anyone else using Family Sharing logs on to a device that is owned by a third party, any information shared within your Family—including calendar, location, photos, and iTunes purchases—may be downloaded on to that third-party device thereby disclosing any such shared information. Visit Family Sharing for more information.

 **The existence of Automated Decision-Making, Including Profiling**

T-MOTOR does not take any decisions involving the use of algorithms or profiling that significantly affects you.

 **Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

T-MOTOR makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and our service specific privacy summaries. When assessing these periods we carefully examine our need to collect personal information at all and if we establish a relevant need we only retain it for the shortest possible period to realize the purpose of collection unless a longer retention period is required by law.

 **Access to Personal Information**

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by signing in to your T-MOTOR ID account page. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access (including a copy) for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if T-MOTOR is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes.We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. We may also decline aspects of deletion or access requests if we believe doing so would undermine our legitimate use of data for anti-fraud and security purposes as described earlier.
